

Gulnaz Zakirova

Cell: 438 936 4243

Email: zakirovagulnaz22@gmail.com

ABOUT ME

Well-organized and processoriented specialist with 3+ years of experience in survey and analyzing data for software development. Strategic mindset that focuses on problem solving tasks and maintaining priorities on strict deadlines.

Highly interested in programming, I'm looking for a position as Programmer Intern to improve my programming skills, utilizing abilities and experiences gained through relevant education and projects.

SKILLS:

Java, C#, C++, VB.NET, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, jQuery, SQL, Data Modeling, Functional and Regression Testing

WORK EXPERIENCE

Junior Project Manager (Jun, 2013 – Oct, 2016) Gorizonty Rosta, Russia

Confer with clients to identify and document requirements

Conduct business and technical studies

Design, develop, integrate and implement information systems business solutions

Provide advice on information systems strategy and management

Functional testing new version of software

Report bugs and errors to development teams

Develop and document software testing plans

Provide technical support to clients

Provide full training for new users

Help Desk Specialist (Feb, 2008 – Aug, 2009) TNG – KomiGIS, Russia

Supporting a network, computer and office equipment

Providing advice to users

Writing reports for "1C:Enterprise" system

EDUCATION

Vanier College (Jan, 2017 – Dec, 2017) Montreal

Software Application Specialist – Continuing Education

Kazan State Technical University (Sept, 2004 – Jan, 2011) Russia

Automated Systems for Information Processing and Control *B.S. Computer Engineering*